SODIQ AYOBAMI ZUBAIR

Plot 6, Ogunbi Layout, Kute, Wofun Area, Ibadan, Oyo State.

Tel: 07069465179, 08111629969 E-mail: <u>ayobamisodiq68@gmail.com</u>

PROFILE

A creative, tech-savvy, honest and resourceful individual with great enthusiasm and determination to succeed. Friendly, good humoured and willing to learn new skills.

What I might lack in experience, I make up for with curiosity and perseverance.

EXPERIENCE

KINGS' MERIDIAN SURVEYS, IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGERIA. 2019 – TILL DATE

Assistant Surveyor

- Assists with operations in the field such as plotting boundaries and diverting traffic in the area.
- Writes the reports of the surveying team's findings.
- Assists and receive training in conducting land and building surveys, including equipment use.
- Use, create, and interpret GPS and computer-aided design (CAD) information.
- Record and enter survey data into databases.

LORAT TECHNOLOGIES, IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGERIA. 2017 - 2018.

Data Entry Clerk

- Compiled, verified accuracy and sorted information according to priorities to prepare source data for computer entry.
- Inserted customer and account data by inputting text based and numerical information from source documents into a computer within time limits.
- Reviewed data for deficiencies or errors, correct any incompatibilities if possible and check output.
- Stored completed work in designated locations and perform backup operations.
- Kept information confidential.
- Responded to gueries for information and access relevant files.
- Complied with data integrity and security policies.

UNITY HIGH SCHOOL, EJIGBO, OSUN STATE, NIGERIA (NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS) 2015 - 2016.

Geography Tutor (Senior Secondary School)

- Taught students the introductory knowledge to Human and Physical Geography.
- Prepared lesson outlines and plans in assigned subject areas with various teaching aids.
- Observed students' performance and record relevant data to assess progress.

NATIONAL BUREAU OF STATISTICS, IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGERIA. 2014.

Intern (Undergraduate)

- Carried out surveys and demarcation of enumerated areas.
- Prepared and submitted reports on activities carried out.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN, IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGERIA Bachelor of Science in Geography (Second Class), 2015

BODIJA INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE, IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGERIA Senior Secondary School Leaving Certificate, 2010

ABIODUN METROPOLITAN NURSERY AND PRIMARY SCHOOL, IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGERIA First School Leaving Certificate, 2004

SKILLS

IT

- Familiar with the fundamentals of frontend web development (HTML, CSS and JavaScript (Vue)).
- Proficient use of Microsoft Office tools as part of my coursework. Also used the internet for research (Assignments, group works, and my project) and know how to search, find and collect relevant background information.
- Introduced to ArcGIS, AutoCAD, Matlab and MySQL (Workbench).

Analytical/Problem Solving

- Possess the ability to clarify the nature of problems, evaluate alternatives, through critical and analytical thinking, and generate new ideas for solving such problems through effective creative thinking.
- Able to draw specific conclusions from a set of general observations or set of facts.
- Capable of reading charts and drawing conclusions from results.

Adaptability

- Capacity to adapt to new situations & settings and an above average level of tolerance for change.
- Flexibility to adapt to the needs of the moment.

Communication

- A developed ability to present opinions and ideas in an open, objective way during the period of my coursework through assigned group projects.
- Also acquired the ability to write clearly and concisely as well as to edit a written text to make sure the message is as clear, concise and as accurate as possible.
- Ability to listen attentively and speak effectively.

Teamwork

- Experienced teamwork from working with different colleagues to prepare and give group presentations on university group assignments.
- Established effective relationships with school colleagues (teachers and support staff) during my National Youth Service Corps placement.

Interpersonal

- Able to interact successfully with a wide range of people.
- Able to empathize with others.

Independence: Possess the ability to do whatever is ask of me efficiently in an independent manner when required.